About 400 people
Happy New Year!
It's the morning chimes, and it's us.
I'm Ellis City.
Let's start the day off right.
That's what we're saying.
It's good, isn't it?
Oh, the girls of the year.
Hi, I'm the new year's daughter!
I'm the New Woman of the Year.
I think I'm going to be older than my years, but usually I just keep climbing and climbing.
Kaho! Kaho!
Did you fall?
I've never seen a girl and a boy this high up in the world.
Kaho's been doing a lot of trousseaulie.
Yeah, I was looking forward to it.
We've been through this before, right?
Yeah, I've grown up that much, but it's like...
It's been fun since I was 12.
Eleven...
Thirteen!
I've been having fun since I was 13.
I'm glad it's been 12 years!
Yes! I'm so glad it's been 12 years!
My question is, what's the difference between being a woman and being anything else?
I feel like it gives me more momentum,
I'm happy about the fictional creature that is Tatoosh, for me.
So I'm really excited, and I think, "What?
I was excited because it was my birthday.
I'm excited about my birthday, but I feel like the whole year is special.
People?
How is Rico actually feeling right now?
I'm not used to feeling that way, so I'm feeling a little sorry for myself.
Reflecting?
On the contrary.
I don't feel like I have that much intention to take it to the next level. I don't have that much intention to take it with me.
I'm not that crazy about it, but I'm going to take it with me.
I think I can be a representative of Tudoshi.
I wonder if I can be.
I think I can be more than anyone else.
A representative of Tudosi.
I am a representative of Tudoshi. I look forward to working with you.
Tudoshi woman.
My pleasure.
The first woman.
First girl. First girl.
Do you have any goals for this year?
What should I do with my first girl? But I want to improve the quality.
What?
I want to improve various human qualities.
Like what?
Like, you know, a woman with too many strings. In the house.
I'm getting a lot of women in my house.
They really don't get out of bed on their days off.
They don't get out of bed unless they really need to.
At least how many steps?
Maybe 10 steps. Maybe 10 steps.
Maybe 10 steps total.
That's not good.
It's not good. So, for now, I'm going to try to get to the minimum human line once.
I would like to improve the quality of my work and try my best to be an attractive person without any hesitation.
I haven't seen your comments, but you are still saying that you are very attractive.
I eat a little. I cook for myself.
I cook for myself, and I usually stir-fry everything with yakiniku sauce.
But it's delicious. It's delicious.
Yes, it is. The taste is the same. So I want to make more elaborate and tastier rice.
But I'm proud of you for making it.
I want to be able to do great things.
It's expensive.
It's expensive, isn't it?
Thanks, I can't go anywhere with 10 steps.
See, I knew it.
Ten steps won't get you anywhere. Ten steps won't get you anywhere.
Then I have it.
See, I told him it's full of charm.
I was right.
Thank you. All right, then. Did you get it?
We've only been at it a little over an hour.
Yes, I did. But I'm trying to improve my overall human skills from that kind of thing.
Oh, Eriko.
Eriko.
What kind of member were you?
I am, well, a woman of the year, but I don't know. But I'm saying,
I wonder.
What I'm saying is, you know, the members take pictures on film. We're going to have a photo exhibition with those pictures. We're going to have a photo exhibition.
Let's do it.
Let's have a photo exhibition.
It's not something you take a picture of and have a meeting about.
Pictures, then, later.
Don't have the meeting here.
And he's still trying to say something.
Also, I want to do a play.
Yeah, I want to do it.
I want to do it.
You sounded like you want to do it.
It's not "I want to do it.
I want to do it.
As for the photo exhibition, I will do it.
We will do it.
Let's do it.
Yes, let's do it.
I'm paying for it with my own money.
Let's do it.
We'll do it on our own.
Please come. Come.
Let's do it.
Yasusun really likes to make something by himself.
I hope it will be a year when I can give back what I got through making music and making music videos by myself.
That's the most honest thing I've ever done.
Thank you very much.
How about you, milio?
What about MILIO?
MILIO started his brand last year,
I'm going to make it bigger.
We are going to make it bigger, and we are also going to do a play.
We are going to do a play.
Now that we have decided on that, I guess we will do an independent production.
I'm going to do an independent production.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm going to do it in Korea, and I'm going to do it in Korea.
Then I'll do something too.
With four people.
And a cameraman.
If it's a play, then a video.
Are you going to do it with Akari?
The two of us will also do it.
But someone should come up with a book, something simple.
Maybe a very small ruby.
If we do something like that.
Let's do it.
I want to do it.
Maybe Meki-san could use some props or something.
We can do it together.
All of us.
Ebichu's 15th anniversary.
I'm looking forward to it.
I can't help it.
Something other than the 10th anniversary. Something other than the 10th anniversary.
I wonder what we are going to do.
I want to do something.
Plus.
I've heard comments about it.
What about Mahoriko?
I want to do a 10th anniversary concert.
Our 10th anniversary is in 4 days.
Four more days.
Was that January 4th?
I miss it.
I wonder what kind of timing we were doing the show.
But, you know, I didn't think anything of it.
I didn't think about it.
At this time of the year? I thought,
I was sure.
I wondered why they played there,
I always wondered.
Maebashi.
I was so tired.
You've already decided to do the 10th anniversary concert on your own.
We'll do it.
You think you can do anything if you say so here, don't you?
Really.
That's true.
It's better to say something.
But Riko is the type of person who doesn't say anything,
But this time, you should.
She's already stopped, you know.
Everyone has stopped.
In Hihara.
If I can't, I'll just go to Hihara.
I'll call out to them myself.
I said, "Come here as a minister.
I put it on the wall.
Display, display.
The best at the end of the station. The best beyond the station.
It's a gutsy exhibit.
It's the best, the best.
This is really, really a photo exhibition.
I love it.
It's Scent of a Child.
It's Scent of a Child, please do it.
I'll do my best.
It would certainly be fun if we all do it together.
We are going to hold the FC in February this time, but it will be produced by the members on a voluntary basis,
It would be nice if we could do that this year.
That's for sure.
Like this year and this year.
We have to think about that too.
It's already this year.
We have a huge climax this time around.
That's right.
The University Welcome Party.
Yes, the welcome party is on January 6 and 7, right?
That's just a little more than a week away.
You'll be in Yokohama again.
Yes, I'm in Yokohama a lot.
It's been a generation, Yokohama.
We've had rehearsals, and it's a lot of fun.
But it's a lot of work.
A lot of things.
I can't tell you what's going on.
I can't say anymore.
If you ask me what the highlight is, I can't say.
We've been rehearsing every day.
I see.
The fall sword is always a lot of fun.
That's right.
I think that's true.
I'm sure you'll see the Fall Sword.
I'd love to, and I still have tickets.
Thank you very much.
6th and 7th, 6th and 7th,
We look forward to seeing you at the Lear Arena MM.
We'll be waiting for you.
That's it, on New Year's Day, like the third New Year's day or something,
I don't know what to do,
I don't have any plans,
If you have no plans, or if you don't feel like New Year's, we will handle everything at once,
We can handle everything at once.
It's a live show where you can get them back.
It's true.
I think that's true,
If you are interested in EBITCHU at today's event....
That's right.
And Momoshiki Uta Gassen, too.
We bought the red group.
We did.
Just now,
You were at KANNAI DEVIL,
I saw your comment,
I saw it,
I couldn't tell if we were the red group of the real Kohaku Uta Gassen or the red group of the Peach Color Uta Gassen,
I couldn't tell if it was the red group of the real Kohaku Uta Gassen or the red group of the Peach Color Uta Gassen,
Please let me know your comment.
I bought the red group, he said.
Oh, I heard it's an award.
And Lady cried.
I see.
From the very beginning,
She cried at the first one of the Knights of Columbus, right?
Yeah, we weren't there.
Oh, no.
I'm so happy for you. Yes, well, at the Montmor Uta Gassen, we sang Blue Diznes, and we participated in the idol medley,
It was fun. It was fun. Finally, I feel the end of the year when I go there.
The closer we get to the end of the year, the more it feels like the end of the year. It's true.
I think there were a lot of idols at the show, but I think I was able to show Ebitu's own color.
I didn't look like anyone. I'm glad. Uji-san, there is one thing I want to ask you.
There were quite a few dressing rooms. There were a lot of idols and people from all walks of life, and they all had their own dressing rooms, didn't they?
Mr. Daiki. Yes, that's right. Daiki. Yes, that's right.
I was just leaving the backstage area to go to the catering.
And, you know, there were so many people there, it would have been dangerous if something had happened, so there were security guards.
That's right. They are very careful, aren't they?
I was in costume, but I was told, "Excuse me, you need a pass to get in,
I had just come out of the dressing room, but I was told that I could not enter without a pass with my picture on it, even though I was hanging up my pose,
I'm a member of this group.
That's amazing.
That's tough.
It's tough.
I had to go out of the dressing room, but it was meaningful.
And, you know, I was rehearsing, I was doing my makeup.
I've said hello to him many times, and he takes his job very seriously, so he's not bad at all.
Even at the center,
I was walking with about three other people,
I see.
I was just ending the conversation by saying, "Camera-chan, you're all alone, you're going to die," or something like that.
And I tend to be accosted by the security guards.
There is a lawn in the center of the venue, and also in the back yard.
If I see this on the lawn, I think, "Oh, I'm sorry, the fans are not this way.
Are you a fan?
I'm a member of that group.
Why, I understand the scale of this event, but it's our event in the center.
Sure, sure.
Did something like that happen at the center?
Oh no, it was something like that, you know.
The members were wearing hoodies.
I was wearing a hoodie.
Yeah, they thought I was, but I was lying down and singing.
It's so embarrassing.
Yeah, that's why.
I didn't expect the members to be lying there.
I just wanted to have fun.
So, I guess I got drunk.
It was like, "Oh my God, they thought we were a cheerful family.
Yes, it was.
Too embarrassing.
Yeah. Yes.
I've already been praised for this.
Well, everyone works hard.
Yes, that's right.
It was great.
It was interesting.
It was funny.
It was a funny big song.
Specialty, blending in with the fans.
Sure.
Funny.
It's funny.
It's something.
How was the idol medley?
It was fun.
Soap bubbles.
The first big role.
Some members were absent today, so a lot of things changed.
There were some sudden changes.
I was very nervous.
After Mr. Moriguchi, right?
Moriguchi-san is a sprout, right?
He's a sprout. And he sings with a nice voice.
I thought it would be after that. I was under a lot of pressure.
Singing "meow".
It's not meow.
I was so nervous.
And I was worried about Daiki because I was the only one.
I was on the lower side. Everyone else was going out by their hair.
I was alone and lonely.
I was shaking when I saw him and wondered if everyone was okay.
I was looking at the screen below.
I'm okay. While walking.
Soap bubbles is something that has a very long history in Halo Pro alone.
Members from all walks of life sang it.
The Halo Pro girls were singing a song that all the other groups had covered. The Halo Pro kids were covering the songs that all the other groups were covering.
It was really fun for us to be able to get that rhythm.
It's a rhythm we don't have.
We don't have it.
We had two steps and 16 seconds.
Aya got really fired up, didn't she?
I'm glad.
You're behind the robot.
Aya was there.
That was great.
That's what I'm talking about.
But the fans were really happy too.
Look at this.
Since the lineup was announced, many of them had been asking me to play soap bubbles, so they were pretty happy.
That's Arline's team, isn't it? Oh, I see.
Isn't it dangerous? But before the Kohaku show, they did a "Boom Boom Pack" in Kohaku.
That was great. It was great.
But you were happy with it. I'm glad.
I'm glad. Arline, the dregs are genius.
Genius, I know. I know.
Yuichi, you're releasing an album in February. That's right.
With a new album called "Brutige".
What kind of ease does "brutigginess" end up being?
It's not dizziness, is it?
Many people call it brutigginess. Many people call it brutigeness, but I thought it was ditheriness.
I thought it was dizziness.
Or blue.
Blue.
Please look forward to the other songs, everyone.
Please take a look.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all this year, and last year was great, right, Ayaka?
It was like, "Please look forward to this year, too.
I was at the peak of sleepiness and my face was bright red and my eyes were red.
Seriously, last year.
I guess it was a note.
He was saying, "Thank you very much for your time," saying he was going to finish the delivery.
Yeah, that's right. Yes.
I don't know why I am so energetic this year.
I'm feeling very energetic this year.
I'm sure of it.
Really?
I think it's because the nights are getting longer.
It's because I've grown up.
No, it's because I'm an adult now.
Yes, but...
I wonder.
I've reached a pretty good age.
Indeed.
That's right.
Yes, it is.
Really?
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you for staying on time. Thank you all.
Thank you very much.
I have an announcement to make today.
Nothing at all?
No, not at all. Not at all.
Notices.
We're at 1,501 members.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
Happy New Year.
Happy New Year!
Hikakin got married.
Hee...
HIKAKIN got married.
Mr. HIKAKIN?
HIKAKIN?
Pronunciation. Pronunciation.
Intonation.
Strange.
One more time.
Hikakin.
Because it's like a picarn.
It was the same feeling as SATSUKI HIKARUN.
He's like Piccaloon.
I'll see you someday.
Hikakin.
He announced it at midnight today.
Oh.
Nice. I'm so happy for you.
Congratulations.
It's something like 1:30 or so. Yes, that's right.
I see. Is that the notice?
No, it's not. What was it?
HIKAKIN got married. What are you talking about?
I'm so happy for you. HIKAKIN?
HIKAKIN? I'm into HIKAKIN.
I didn't expect to hear so much news.
What are you going to say for the next 5 minutes?
Do you think the younger members are asleep?
I think they're awake.
What are they doing?
Are they taking a break?
What are they going to do if they're asleep?
I feel sorry for them.
Power harassment, power harassment.
I'm sure he'll be up there.
Aren't you tired? Today.
You're up early.
It was early.
Why early?
Is it the earliest this year?
In the 31st.
But I was thinking about the rehearsal.
I had a lot of work to do today because of Jae's member's thing, but I'm not sure how much time I have left, I know there was a bit of a flurry of activity today because of the Jae members,
In the past, there were a lot of places that were more integrated.
That's for sure.
I don't have enough time to do that.
My head might have been full.
Was there room to spare?
Except for the idol medley, I don't think there was that much going on this time.
It looked like it.
I'm sure.
But, well, even Weil is a young child.
I do that every year.
It's really amazing.
I think I'm doing something that's not easy to do.
I can't call you, Maya.
Please go to sleep.
You all should sleep.
Please sleep, too.
I'm not feeling well, you know,
Everyone will not call the three of you tonight.
Kanae DeVille was fun.
I will not call the members who are not on the phone.
They may be sleeping.
Sorry about the soap bubbles, Maya-san.
Mayasa's position and the monk's position were back and forth.
The camera work would have definitely taken them out of the picture.
Because it's Mabutuchi.
I look forward to working with you as a friend.
Yes, I'm looking forward to working with you as a friend.
That's right. The end of the museum debiri was too interesting. It's true.
Suddenly. Was it Wasaka?
Suddenly, he started the question-and-answer session. I thought the question-and-answer session would end with Ria's,
I thought it would end with Ria's one. Excuse me.
I'm sorry, Saopon, but it might be a little sad. Just a little more.
Wait a little longer, that's all.
That's right.
Even the master was surprised.
But it was amazing. The live broadcast went by so fast today.
Didn't it? It was delicious. It wasn't? It was delicious.
So the cherry twist was good? Thickness?
I don't know. Maybe it's the thinness, maybe it's the thickness, maybe it's the thickness,
The thickness is thick, but... I don't know, maybe the width of the noodle, maybe it's not that wide.
The width was thick, but the length was thin, so it was easy to eat. It was really delicious.
Also, the soba flavor was amazing because of the large area.
It was really amazing.
I wanted to say something like, "What are they, gummy bears?
But I couldn't say it.
It was delicious.
But he apologized to me. I was changing my clothes before I left for work,
I was getting dressed before I left for work, and he said, "Miru-chan, I think I'm going to eat soba today.
He said, "Don't tell me.
He said I was being very prodigal.
Are you going to tell me everything?
It'll be fun.
Yuu probably had fun picking vegetables, too,
She picked carrots and radishes,
And cauliflower.
Is she saying all of them?
All of them.
Tell Miru once.
He says it's hard to react.
I'm going to tell her one more time.
I've already said it once, haven't I?
Yes, I did.
It was delicious. It was delicious.
The green onions were delicious.
The green onions were sweet, weren't they? Yes, they were.
They were big and delicious. The vegetables from that farm are really delicious.
They were sweet. The vegetables were good.
The vegetables were so delicious.
The way they cut them, the way they cut them, the way they cut them, the way they cut them, the way they cut them, the way they cut them, the way they cut them.
Everyone was precise, but it was really precise. It was really tight.
Yes, they were cutting very evenly, just like that.
It was probably the burr method. It's interesting, isn't it? And yet, that's why I felt that Sakuragi's work was better.
It's like tracing. I felt like I was tracing. It's something to trace. Yeah, it's interesting.
It's interesting. The weeds are delicious.
Saba-san, Mayu-san, anyone want to play with the curzer?
Me and Rika do it, and then it becomes, you know, thick, like gummy bears.
It's like gummy bears. What was it again?
The two of us. We were doing it together.
I wonder if it was the difference in rice. I remember someone praising me for that. Like the rice was good.
But, what was it? What was it?
That's important.
Yes, that's right, something. Heh.
It's a burr.
But, you know, they all united, and it became shorter, right? Yeah.
So, you know, I eat it all the time, and it's really hard to do. I don't know how to say it.
They were all shortened like this. But, you know, it was pretty much like this.
It was folded up. When this one is long, it doesn't look like this. Ah.
Heh, interesting. I did my best.
Aya, Mire-chan, Mo-chan, Riko, it's the new year. Congratulations!
Congratulations to all of you.
In 2024, it will be the 11th year of the Ebichu family. I love the ever-evolving Ebichu, they are so cool. One more time.
It's been 11 years. Thank you very much.
We'll be waiting for you.
Oh, it's about time for an announcement. Oh, that's okay.
So, shall we sit down?
Oh, there you are.
I have an announcement, uh... I have an announcement.
Oh, my gosh, oh my gosh, we've decided on Theater Shrimp.
Yay! It's here! Yay!
I wanted to do it. I wanted to do it.
I've been wanting to do it.
And the title is My Sweet Little Lucky Day!
Yay!
Cute, cute.
And what a surprise, only 10 members of Ebichu will perform this time.
Eeeee!
What, what, what is it?
Seriously? Theater Shrimp, well, if you've never been here before, you may not know this,
Yes, it's true.
Actually, this is the first time we are doing a show with only 10 people. Actually, this is the first time for us to do it with only 10 people.
That's right.
I would like to do it as a member-authority.
Yes, it's the first time.
It's the first time.
The performance dates are from March 9 to March 17, for a total of 11 stages.
Yes, that's right.
The scriptwriter and director is Ryoichi Tsuchiya, whom you know well.
We will meet again.
We meet again.
We did the last one together.
If we had done it together, we would have had to do it together.
Because towards the end, I kept thinking, "What should I do with the title?
I don't know.
I see.
Here is the title that came to mind.
Yes. And after this, at 26:00, 2:00 a.m., right?
Yes.
Ebichu FC will start accepting advance reservations at 2:00 a.m. on the day of the show,
I hope you will come and see the 10 members of Ebichu performing together.
I'm so happy for all of you.
Yay!
I'm so happy.
I really wanted to do this.
I really wanted to do it.
And there were a lot of people waiting for the theater series, right?
Yeah.
The last one was just in Corona.
Yes, that's right.
No, it wasn't.
What's that?
No?
It was a long time ago.
It's going to be a Corona.
It's already something.
It was a long time ago. Long time ago.
Huh?
Six years ago?
Yes, yes, yes.
Maybe six or seven years ago.
About six years ago.
Wow.
We were all active students, and we played student roles and stuff.
Like 3rd graders.
Like 3rd grade.
Junior high school, junior high school, the year we started.
Junior 2, junior 3.
Junior high, junior high.
I went to the graduation ceremony.
You know, the rehearsal.
That's right.
It was March, right? So, it was like final exams and graduation ceremony, right?
That's right, that's right.
That's right.
Where is the place?
Location, right, location.
Oh, Sunshine Ikebukuro.
That's it.
Sunshine Theater in Ikebukuro.
It's at the Sunshine Theater in Ikebukuro.
It's a big capacity.
It's a big capacity, so I thought people would come.
Yes, I did.
I'll do my best.
We did it before at Sunshine.
It's a really easy venue to see, so I hope everyone will come.
Also, the best thing about Theater Shrimp is that if you see it only once, it's hard to know what it's like,
If you come several times, you will discover new things about the work.
I think it will be a work with new discoveries if you come again and again.
I'm glad to hear that. I'm glad.
I'm looking forward to it.
I did a bit with Emma last time.
And, well, have you seen Kazami? I've never seen Kunitomo and Sakuragi. That's for sure.
I don't think you have seen them either.
They did workshops and stuff like that, and it was pretty interesting.
Ten people always go to share, and each of them has a very strong character. So there are 10 of them, right?
How will it all fit together? Isn't it too much?
It's just too much, isn't it?
It's a world I can't even imagine.
And since we only have the Leviticus members, we'll have to do something with all of us.
That's right. There are no professionals, you know, actors.
No, they are all professionals. That's right. The actors,
That's right. Because we don't have the funny older men that you are familiar with.
That's right. But there are people who perform on various stages, especially here in this world,
I think you could make the most of the various productions you've been given.
I'll do my best. Per my own thing.
Per my own thing. I will do my best to show what I have pledged.
I'm looking forward to it.
Comment.
What do you think? Of course, some of you may know of it, but have any of you seen the Theater Series yet?
I'm sure there are people out there. Yes, I think so. Most of them have never seen it.
I'm in Amakura. You can see Machiko, too, so if you want, you can see Machiko Osanaki.
Machiko Osanaki.
It says here that you're in the realm of Starbucks.
Indeed.
Well, think of it as an acting agency. Acting agency.
I, I thought it was an actor's office.
Yes, room muso.
I would love to have you all come soon.
So, I'm doing Pialina in January, SC in February, album release, and Theatre Cynic in March.
So many things to do.
Lots and lots of things.
We have to keep the momentum up.
Yes, as Satsuma-san.
Let's go GOGO! Let's go GOGO!
Let's GOGO!
Well, Katsuno-san, you're looking good at the end.
What? Is it OK if I finish already?
Yes.
Please make the cake look good.
Well then, everyone, I wish you all a happy new year.
Good night!
Bye bye!
Momoreenu!
I'll be waiting for you on the 6th and so on!
We'll be waiting for you!
It's Pialina FM! Everybody get together!
We are waiting for you!
I couldn't say anything nice about the cake at all.
I'm glad you liked it.
Really?
Thank you.